[{"answer": "Well, I think some are very serious people.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Do you think that they have justification for their anger?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "I sort of think it's cool.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "And how do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, you always say that but they were duped into doing mortgages.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "In other words, how much is personal responsibility got to come in to play when it comes to finances?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Well, some of the banks are asking for fees just to keep your money.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "What do you think of that, in particular?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, the biggest problem I have with what's happening with the system is the banks, unless you're like somebody like me -- if I want to borrow money, I can borrow all the money I want at the very -- at the rates that are the lowest rates I have ever seen.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "What do you agree with?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "RUMP: They have the money.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "But they have the money, right?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Part of the problem that the banks have, in all fairness, Piers -- now I'm not a huge fan of the banks because I see what's happening.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "How do you get through this apparently immovable wall now where the banks have the money but don't want to lend it and the economy is just trapped in hell?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "You have to let the banks do their thing.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Is there more that Barack Obama can do as president to unlock this, to move the paralysis?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Well, I'll tell you this.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Did you agree with the bailing out of the banks after Lehman Brothers collapsed?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Well -- well, because they didn't really -- I mean, when you think of it, they got very cheap money and they paid it back.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "What do you say to that argument?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, that was the other argument.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Should the government have done that?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Well, I think, first of all, they have some very good people running, and I've become friendly with some of them.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Why have you become this talisman for them and what are you making of the Republican race at the moment?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "We're weak.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "But how much of this is done to America just being at the moment oddly inherently weak?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, the environmental approvals are impossible.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Why has America stopped doing that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "The bureaucracy is unbelievable.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Bureaucracy is crazy here, right?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Why can't the bureaucracy be eliminated?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "It can't be eliminated but it could certainly be made a lot quicker and a lot better and a lot more efficient.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Why can't somebody get a grip of that?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Well, I have to start off by saying I think any of them would be better than what we have now.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "So which of all these Republican candidates at the moment do you think has it in him to get America out of this mess?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Well, look.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "How big a problem is this for the Republicans, that the guy that most people think is probably the best option can't get the right kind of traction?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Nobody knows.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Why is it, do you think?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Is he a bit dull?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "I think he's a terrific guy.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "What do you make of him?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Does Herman -- could Herman Cain do that?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "It doesn't help anything, does it?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "You know it's sort of interesting.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "No, I don't necessarily.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Do you accept that what he produced is valid?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "But you believe he probably was born in America?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I say he might have been.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's good for him in the Republican primary.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Is it a sensible thing for him to do?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Well, it's --", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Yes, what do you make of him?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "I don't know what happened because when you're with him he's great.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Because -- I mean in the debates he's pretty shocking, isn't he?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "He is different.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Is he -- is he articulate?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "I'd love to.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Are you interviewing him?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I would.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Can you put in a good word?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "RUMP: I'm looking.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Isn't that exactly the kind of environment you were thinking about and is it possible, given where we are, that you might still run?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a very bad time to be raising taxes.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "You're a big employer.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "They're not going to get a job and they take that -- them off the unemployment number?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Thousands, tens of thousands of people.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Well, I have two primary ways.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "What is the simple way to stimulate growth and jobs?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "That's true.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "One of the great business men and creator that this country ever produced, right?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "I do have stuff made.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "Do you have any stuff, I guess, made for you and your companies in China?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Well, a lot because when you build a building, I mean --", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "A lot?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Well, I'll tell you this.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "What would you say?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "It was very interesting because it was supposed to be about me, and then I looked at the script, I said, I don't want that about me.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Something you want to tell me?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "No, I haven't, but I hope she does well.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "Have you sent flowers?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "I think Oprah is great.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Now what do you think of Oprah?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "RUMP: I think we have a country that has tremendous untapped potential.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "Is that part of the problem?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "Well, again, I think the country has unbelievable potential, almost greater than before, if we allow it to happen.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "What should the new American dream, the realistic one, be now?", "qSentId": 754}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "And it would seem to me with a population now of, what, seven billion?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "Well, I've never been a big fan of the name \"grandfather,\" but that's what I am.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "How are you enjoying this new -- this new outburst of young Trumps?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "They're really good.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 827, "question": "Are they all fresh faced, excited?", "qSentId": 826}, {"answer": "Well, I think ultimately it's all about family.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 841, "question": "What does family mean to you?", "qSentId": 840}, {"answer": "I think the thing that drives me is I love what I'm doing.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 850, "question": "Is there a remaining great ambition you have?", "qSentId": 849}, {"answer": "Well, I think somebody that did a really good job aesthetically, I've gotten tremendous reviews on buildings and courses and clubs and all of the things I build, it's very important to me, the aesthetic, but also somebody that's put lots of people to work and created lots of happy families.", "docId": "111030pmt", "aSentId": 874, "question": "How would you like to be remembered?", "qSentId": 873}]